all right I can't stop and I don't think
I've ever had a day where I've had this
much energy you're a long time but I've
always kind of known that my energy and
health levels are related to me
following my purpose so it makes sense
so Apple number 27 is a dating app so
stone exists and I think we need to
create more of them I do actually think
we need to create one for people for the
people by the people so using the
process that I talked about in number 26
deciding what we want and the joy of a
lot of these things you can make more
niche broad products so if you have a
niche in the dating market which a lot
of us do you're gay if you are trans if
you are anything besides a sis hetero if
you want to look at the truth is there's
a lot of gay apps and stuff out there
too now but what about bisexuals and
pansexuals and poly people and what
about people who really suck at the
getting a significant other but aren't
so bad at p1 and helping like if the
purpose of a dating app is to get people
together in meaningful relationships of
two or more people that are compatible
and enhance both their lives then we can
create a system that maximizes that and
isn't for profit so you're not looking
to get the most people together and then
get them to break up and get back into
the loop again because I'm people in the
dating market is what you're looking for
they're they're not looking to create if
you're looking to create a hook-up app
and a sex app that most of them become
then at least you're honestly doing that
you're looking at what's your sexuality
and what are you into and who else is
into those things and they'd be better
if we created it together and it was
designed for all of us and this app one
of the 27